Francesco Sangalli, Junior Front End Developer | Salesforce Developer

Milan, Italy, +39 3314335283, ilgallofranc@gmail.com

LINKS

Portfolio: https://fsangalli-portfolio-dev-ed.my.site.com/

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/francesco-sangalli-4700091a7/

Github: https://github.com/FrancescoSangalli

PROFILE

Front End and Salesforce Developer focused on Javascript related tech with more than 1 year of experience in tech/consultancy. Avid Learner who enjoys contribuiting to the world through code. Good team worker both remotly and on site.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Javascript, SASS, Bootstrap, Tailwind css, Webpack, React, Redux, Git, Github, Apex, Visualforce Pages, Lightning Components (Aura, LWC)

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

IT Consultant, Lobra srl, May 2022 - Present

- Technical Analysis
- Salesforce Developer (Full Stack)
- Salesforce Administrator
- Contributed to various projects with different activities like: technical analysis, data modeling, process automation using flow, Apex triggers, and Apex classes, custom components using Aura and LWC frameworks and PDF generation through Visualforce pages

Administartive Secretary, Centro Sportivo Bonacossa, Feb 2021 – Dec 2021

- Excel
- Payments
- Documents Archive

Basketball Instructor, Istituto Zaccaria, Oct 2020 – Jan 2022

EDUCATION

Junior Front End Developer Certificate, start2impact, Apr 2022

Projects on Github: Personal Portfolio, Counter, Air Pollution Meter, Book Library, Film Library (final project)

Experis Academy Salesforce Consultant, Experis Academy, Apr 2022

Salesforce Sales, Service, Marketing and Commerce Cloud, Salesforce Admin, Apex, Lightning Components

Academy Salesforce Developer, NTT Data, Feb 2022

Salesforce Sales and Service Cloud, Salesforce Admin, Apex, Lightning Components

Economics, Università degli Studi di Milano-Bicocca, Oct 2013 – Present

Diploma Liceo Scientifico, Liceo Salvador Allende, Jul 2013

HOBBIES

Basketball, Soccer, Programming, Books